<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Huda_Application</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string name="password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="Login">Login</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword">Forgot Password? <b>Reset</b></string>
    <string name="dontAccount">Don\'t Have an Account? <b>Sign Up</b></string>
    <string name="alreadyAccount">Already Registered? <b>Sign In</b></string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="language">English</string>
    <string name="FirstName">Enter First Name</string>
    <string name="LastName">Enter Last Name</string>
    <string name="EnterEmail">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="EnterPass">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="Reenter">Re-enter Password</string>
    <string name="reset">Send Reset</string>
    <string name="loginHeader">ACCOUNT LOGIN</string>
    <string name="registerHeader">REGISTER ACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="forgotPassHeader">RESET PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="login_dialog">Enter your credentials below to log in.</string>
    <string name="regDiaglogue">Complete the fields below to register an account. You will receive a verification email upon successful registration.</string>
    <string name="forgotDialogue">Enter the email associated with your account and you will receive instructions to reset your password.</string>

    <!--    Main Menu Page-->
    <string name="home">HOME</string>
    <string name="Annoucment">ANNOUNCEMENTS</string>
    <string name="services">SERVICES</string>
    <string name="story">OUR STORY</string>
    <string name="partners">PARTNERS</string>
    <string name="contact">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="patients_page">APPOINTMENTS</string>
    <string name = "logout">Logout</string>

    <!--    New Login / Services-->
    <string name="healthservices">Free Health Services</string>
    <string name="PrimaryNewLogin"><u>PRIMARY</u></string>
    <string name="MentalNewLogin"><u>MENTAL</u></string>
    <string name="VisionNewLogin"><u>VISION</u></string>
    <string name="DentalNewLogin"><u>DENTAL</u></string>
    <string name="SpecialityNewLogin"><u>SPECIALTY</u></string>
    <string name="HaveAnAccount">Have An Account?</string>
    <string name="DontHaveAnAccount">Don\'t Have An Account?</string>
    <string name="SignUp">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="PrimaryCare">PRIMARY CARE</string>
    <string name="MentalCare">MENTAL CARE</string>
    <string name="VisionHealth">VISION CARE</string>
    <string name="Dental">DENTAL CARE</string>
    <string name="speciality">SPECIALTY CARE</string>

    <!--    Inbox Page-->
    <string name="Inbox">INBOX</string>

    <!--    Patient Portal-->
    <string name="NewPatient">New Patient</string>
    <string name="patientForm">New Patient Form</string>
    <string name="checkIn">Check-in</string>
    <string name="MedicalChart">Medical Chart</string>

    <!--    Patient Form Strings -->
    <string name="Registration">REGISTRATION</string>
    <string name="Date">Date (MM-DD-YY)</string>
    <string name="VisitReason">Visit Reason</string>
    <string name="Sex">Sex</string>
    <string name="DOB">DOB (MM-DD-YYYY)</string>
    <string name="Address">Address (1234 Street St.)</string>
    <string name="City">City</string>
    <string name="State">State</string>
    <string name="ZipCode">Zip Code</string>
    <string name="SSN">SSN (123-12-1234)</string>
    <string name="HomePhone">Home Phone (123-123-1234)</string>
    <string name="CellPhone">Cell Phone (123-123-1234)</string>
    <string name="PreferredNumber">Preferred Number (Home or Mobile)</string>
    <string name="ConsentToCall">Consent to Call? (Yes or No)</string>
    <string name="ConsentToText">Consent to Text? (Yes or No)</string>
    <string name="InsuranceProvider">Insurance Provider</string>
    <string name="Email">Email (Same as Registration Email)</string>

    <string name="SelectRace">Please Select a Race:</string>
    <string name="Black">Black/African American</string>
    <string name="White">White/Caucasian</string>
    <string name="Asian">Asian</string>
    <string name="MiddleEastern">Middle Eastern/North African</string>
    <string name="Hispanic">Hispanic/Latino</string>
    <string name="NativeAmerican">Native American</string>
    <string name="NativeHawaiian">Native Hawaiian or Other Pacific Islander</string>

    <string name="SelectEthnicity">Please Select an Ethnicity:</string>
    <string name="HispanicEthnicity">Hispanic or Latino/a</string>
    <string name="NotHispanicEthnicity">Not Hispanic or Latino/a</string>
    <string name="PreferredLanguage">Preferred Language</string>
    <string name="Translator">Translator Needed? (Yes or No)</string>
    <string name="SocialInfo">The following information does NOT affect your right to care at HUDA, but it is needed to continue providing our free services.</string>

    <string name="MaritalStatus">Marital Status</string>
    <string name="HouseholdIncome">Household Income</string>


    <string name="Every">Every</string>
    <string name="Week">Week</string>
    <string name="TwoWeeks">Two Weeks</string>
    <string name="Months">Month</string>
    <string name="Year">Year</string>
    <string name="HouseholdSize">Household Size</string>

    <string name="EmploymentStatus">Employment Status</string>
    <string name="Unemployed">Unemployed</string>
    <string name="EmployedFullTime">Employed (Full Time)</string>
    <string name="EmployedPartTime">Employed (Part Time)</string>
    <string name="SelfEmployed">Self-Employed</string>
    <string name="Student">Student</string>
    <string name="Retired">Retired</string>
    <string name="SeekingEmployment">Seeking Employment</string>
    <string name="Occupation">Occupation</string>
    <string name="VeteranStatus">Are you a Veteran?</string>
    <string name="EmergencyContact">Emergency Contact Information</string>
    <string name="EmergencyContactName">Name</string>
    <string name="RelationshipToPatient">Relationship to Patient</string>
    <string name="EmergencyContactPhone">Contact Phone (123-123-1234)</string>
    <string name="I">I,</string>
    <string name="PatientConsent">voluntarily accept treatment/counseling as recommended and
explained by the HUDA staff. I understand that I am free to withdraw my consent and discontinue treatment at any time.
In addition, I have been informed of my rights to refuse to participate in research activities. I understand that I have rights
as a recipient of free services provided by the HUDA Clinic. I have been advised on the HUDA Clinic’s NO CALL NO SHOW
Policy regarding primary care and specialty services and agree to follow it. Further, I have been advised of the Federal
Confidentiality Regulation and been given a copy of the Confidentiality Notice to review.</string>
    <string name="YourName">Your Name</string>
    <string name="VoluntaryConsent">voluntarily accept treatment/counseling as recommended </string>
    <string name="PatientNamePrinted">Patient Name (Printed)</string>
    <string name="PatientSignature">Patient/Guardian Signature</string>
    <string name="TodayDate">Date (MM-DD-YYYY)</string>
    <string name="SubmitForm">Submit</string>
    <string name="NextForm">Next Form</string>


    <!--Appointment Check-In Page-->
    <string name="FullName">Full Name</string>
    <string name="Birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="AppointmentTime">Appointment Time</string>
    <string name="EnterCheckinEmail">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="CheckInButton">Check-In</string>

    <!--    Contact Us Page-->
    <string name="ContactUsHeader">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="ContactUsPara">HUDA, a Free Community Health Clinic\nin Metro Detroit</string>
    <string name="CallHeader">Call:</string>
    <string name="ClinicPhone">(313) 865-8446</string>
    <string name="AddressHeader">Address:</string>
    <string name="ClinicAddress">13240 Woodrow Wilson St.\nDetroit, MI 48238</string>
    <string name="SocialMediaHeader">Find Us On:</string>

    <!--    Our Story Page-->
    <string name="OurStoryHeader">OUR STORY</string>
    <string name="History">HISTORY OF THE HUDA CLINIC</string>
    <string name="HistoryPara">HUDA Clinic first opened its doors in May 2004 to serve the uninsured population of the Detroit area. The clinic initially operated on funds gathered by the Muslim community of Metro Detroit.</string>
    <string name="HistPara">When it began, the HUDA Clinic provided solely medical services. We then moved from our original facility at the Muslim Center of Detroit into a new, larger facility on Woodrow Wilson Street. Since then, we have expanded our care to include a full range of dental, vision care, podiatry, and mental health services, as well as a plethora of specialty services available at no-cost to our patients. Our new facility has allowed us to expand our services and our service times, but none of that would be possible without the generous support of our donors and volunteers.</string>

    <!--    Announcements Page-->
    <string name="AnnouncementsHeader">ANNOUNCEMENTS</string>
    <string name="ClosureHeader">2022 Holiday Closure Dates</string>
    <string name="Date1">Wednesday November 23, 2022 - Monday November 28th , 2022</string>
    <string name="Date2">Saturday December 24th, 2022</string>
    <string name="Date3">Saturday December 31st, 2022</string>
    <string name="Event1">Thanksgiving</string>
    <string name="Event2">Christmas Eve</string>
    <string name="Event3">New Year\'s Eve</string>
    <string name="CalendarHeader">Clinic Calendar</string>
    <string name="appointmentsHeader">APPOINTMENTS</string>

    <!--  ############################################  !->
    <!-        Health Services-->
    <!--  ############################################  -->


    <!--    Primary Services Page-->
    <string name="PrimaryServicesHeader">PRIMARY SERVICES</string>
    <string name="PrimaryCarePar1">Primary care providers are typically the first line of contact for patients; treating general health concerns, providing education, medications and specialty referrals as needed.</string>
    <string name = "HealthAssessments">Health Assessments</string>
    <string name = "IllnessManagement">Acute and Chronic Illness Management</string>
    <string name = "LabServices">Laboratory Services</string>
    <string name = "NoCostPharm">No Cost Pharmacy</string>
    <string name = "DiabetesScreening">Diabetes Screening and Treatment</string>
    <string name = "CholBP">Cholesterol and Blood Pressure Screenings</string>
    <string name = "HealthEd">Health Education and Resources</string>
    <string name ="servicesInclude">SERVICES INCLUDE</string>

    <!--    Dental Health Page-->
    <string name="DentalHealthHeader">DENTAL CARE</string>
    <string name="DentalHealthPar1">Many people wait to have necessary dental work done because they don’t have insurance, however small dental problems can quickly become incredibly painful if left alone. Come in to HUDA for cleanings, fillings, extractions and exams to keep your teeth healthy and receive a referral to a specialist if needed.</string>
    <string name="DentalScreenings">Dental Screenings and X-Rays</string>
    <string name="DeepCleanings">Deep Cleanings</string>
    <string name="CompositeFillings">Composite Fillings</string>
    <string name="ToothExtractions">Tooth Extractions</string>

    <!--    Vision Care Page-->
    <string name="VisionCareHeader">VISION CARE</string>
    <string name="VisionCarePar1">Vision screenings are an effective method to identify individuals with visual impairment or eye conditions that are likely to lead to vision loss. We perform screenings in-house and provide no-cost eye wear and referrals to low-cost local ophthalmologists as needed.</string>
    <string name ="Glaucoma">Glaucoma Screenings</string>
    <string name ="Cataract">Cataract Screenings</string>
    <string name ="Macular">Macular Degeneration Screenings</string>
    <string name ="EyeWear">FREE Eye-Wear</string>

    <!--    Mental Health Page-->
    <string name="MentalHealthHeader">MENTAL HEALTH</string>
    <string name="MentalHealthPar1">We have psychiatrists on staff along with our licensed social workers to provide therapy and treatment for a wide range of mental health concerns. We offer free counseling and treatment to veterans, homeless, uninsured, and the working underinsured.</string>
    <string name="Psych">Psychiatrists On Site</string>
    <string name="AdultCounseling">Adult Counseling</string>
    <string name="AnxietyandDep">Anxiety and Depression</string>
    <string name="Bipolar">Bipolar Disorders</string>
    <string name="Eating">Eating Disorders</string>
    <string name="Schiz">Schizoaffective Disorders</string>
    <string name="AndMore">And More</string>

    <!--    Speciality Care Page-->
    <string name="SpecialtyCareHeader">SPECIALTY SERVICES</string>
    <string name ="SpecialityCarePar1">Within the field of medicine, there are many sub-specialties when coordinating care to patients. At HUDA, we provide a range of specialty care and consultations to our patients, with the aim of expanding access to healthcare services. All specialty services require a referral from a HUDA primary care provider.</string>
    <string name="PhysTherapy">Physical Therapy</string>
    <string name="Endocrinology">Endocrinology</string>
    <string name="Cardiology">Cardiology</string>
    <string name="Podiatry">Podiatry</string>
    <string name="Nephrology">Nephrology</string>
    <string name="Gastroenterology">Gastroenterology</string>
    <string name="ENT">Ear, Nose, Throat (ENT)</string>
    <string name="Hepatology">Hepatology</string>
    <string name="Hematology">Hematology</string>
    <string name="Pulmonology">Pulmonology</string>


<!--Announcements Page-->
    <string name="prevMonthButton"><![CDATA[<-]]></string>
    <string name="nextMonthButton"><![CDATA[->]]></string>
    <string name="PrevMonthButton"><![CDATA[<-]]></string>
    <string name="calItem">1</string>

    <!--Patient Contract-->
    <string name="PatientContractHeader">Patient Contract</string>
    <string name="PatientContractHeader2">AUTHORIZATION FOR MEDICAL TREATMENT AT CLINIC. READ CAREFULLY - THIS IS A CONTRACT</string>
    <string name="PatientContractBody">I consent to receiving services at the Health Unit on Davison Avenue, henceforth referred to as HUDA Clinic. Services may include assessment, routine diagnostic procedures, medications, lab tests, and appropriate medical treatment as the attending Physician/Nurse practitioner/Physician\’s Assistant considers necessary for my care. I understand that the practice of medicine is not an exact science and I acknowledge that I have received no guarantees regarding the result of examination or treatment at this clinic. I understand that the services I receive at HUDA Clinic or because of a referral from HUDA Clinic are being provided by health care practitioners and lay volunteers who are not receiving compensation and compensation will not be requested from any source. I understand, as provided by Federal and Michigan State Law (Michigan Public Health Code. MCL 333.16277), that these volunteers are not liable for civil damages because of acts or omissions which may occur while providing services to me. I understand that any fees incurred for referrals or any orders to an outside facility, from HUDA Clinic are my responsibility. I agree to be tested for blood borne pathogens in case of inadvertent exposure to blood and/or body fluids as recommended by the Centers for Disease Control. I understand that any verbally abusive or threatening behavior to the clinic staff or other patients is grounds for the termination of clinic services. Falsifying my income or medical insurance information, whether private or public provided, is grounds for termination of clinic services.</string>
    <string name="PatientContractBody2">I understand HUDA clinic’s No Call No Show policy which states for Primary Care</string>
    <string name="PatientContractBody3">A. If I do not keep a scheduled appointment and do not call to cancel or reschedule with reasonable notice, I will only be eligible to be seen as a Walk-In for the following visit.</string>
    <string name="PatientContractBody4">B. If I have 3 or more No Call No Shows in a 12-month period, I could face termination of clinic services. I understand HUDA Clinic’s No Call No Show policy for Specialty Care (All appointments that are NOT primary care including., but not limited to Dental, Endocrinology, Psychiatry, ENT Optometry… etc.).</string>
    <string name="PatientContractBody5">C. If I do not keep a scheduled appointment and do not call to cancel or reschedule with a reasonable time, I will need to find alternatives for my specialty care needs.</string>
    <string name="PatientContractBody6">D. If I do not keep 2 scheduled specialty care appointments within a 6-month period, you won’t be permitted to schedule further specialty services and could face termination of clinic services.</string>
    <string name="PatientContractBody7">My signature below constitutes my acknowledgement that I understand this request for consent and that I agree to its contents.</string>

    <!--Patient Auth for release information-->
    <string name="AuthFormHeader">HUDA Authorization for Release of Information</string>
    <string name="AuthFormBody">Occasionally it is necessary for the HUDA Clinic to consult with other providers, such as specialists or other facilities, such as hospitals or labs to provide you, our patient, with what our providers believe to be the most appropriate course of action for your treatment. By signing this form, you give us, HUDA Clinic, permission to share your pertinent medical information with other providers/facilities to best complete your treatment or request medical records from previous providers on your behalf.</string>
    <string name="AuthFormBody2">I, the patient, hereby authorize HUDA Clinic and its affiliates, its employees and agents, to use and disclose protected health information (e.g. information relating to the diagnosis, treatment, and health care services provided or to be provided to me and which identifies my name, address, social security number, date of birth) for the purpose of helping to coordinate my medical care. I understand that any personal health information or other information released to the person or organization identified above may be subject to re-disclosure by such person/organization and may be no longer protected by applicable federal and state privacy laws. I understand that I have a right to revoke this authorization by providing written notice to HUDA Clinic at any time. However, this authorization may not be revoked if its employees or agents have taken action on this authorization prior to receiving my written notice. I also understand I have the right to have a copy of this authorization.I further understand that this authorization is voluntary and that I may refuse to sign this authorization. I also understand that should I refuse to sign this form I greatly limit the services that HUDA Clinic will be able to perform for me. I understand that should I refuse to sign this,the HUDA Clinic will not be able to prescribe me medication to any pharmacy, nor be able to provide me with any lab work, physician referrals or medical record requests.</string>
    <string name="AuthFormBody3">We take protecting your identity very seriously and do not share any unnecessary information with any of our partners.</string>

    <!--Patient personal representative -->
    <string name="PersonRepHeader">Designation of Personal Representative</string>
    <string name="PersonRepBody">Completing this form allows the person designated to receive protected health information (PHI) such as test results. It also permits the personal representative to request and receive a patient\'s medical records.</string>
    <string name="PersonRepBody2">A personal representative is not the same as a healthcare agent who is allowed to make medical decisions on the patient’s behalf.</string>
    <string name="PersonRepBody3">I designate the following person(s) below as my personal representative(s) and understand and acknowledge that this designation gives the Personal Representative(s) the same power over my protected health information as I have, including the right to inspect my records, authorize disclosures and request restrictions and amendments. I hereby waive any restrictions on my personal representative(s)’ access to my protected health information. I understand that I am not required to list anyone. I also understand that this designation shall remain in place until such time as I revoke it in writing by letter to the Privacy Officer of HUDA Clinic.</string>
    <string name="PersonRepHeader2">Personal Representatitve(s)</string>
    <string name="PersonRep">Print Name</string>
    <string name="Relation">Relationship to Patient</string>
    <string name="PhoneNumber">Phone Number 123–123–1234</string>

    <!-- Stress Form -->
    <string name="StressFormHeader">Stress\n Questionaire</string>
    <string name="StressFormbody">Over the last two (2) weeks, how often have you been bothered by any of the following problems? Please input the number that applies to you</string>
    <string name="StressFormInstruction">0 = Not at all\n1 = Several Days\n2 = More than half the days\n3 = Nearly everyday</string>
    <string name="Q1S1">1. Feeling down, depressed or hopeless</string>
    <string name="StressFormAnswer">Enter 0, 1, 2 or 3</string>
    <string name="q2s1">2. Trouble falling or stay asleep or\n Sleeping too much</string>
    <string name="q3s1">3. Feeling tired or having little\n energy</string>
    <string name="q4s1">4. Poor appetite OR Overeating</string>
    <string name="q5s1">5. Feeling bad about yourself or\n what that you are a failure or \n have let yourself or your family\n down</string>
    <string name="q6s1">6. Trouble concentrating on things such\n as reading the newspaper or \n watching television</string>
    <string name="q7s1">7. Moving or speaking so slowly\n that other \npeople could have noticed OR\nBeing so fidgety or restless that you’ve\n been moving around a lot more\n than usual</string>
    <string name="q8s1">8. Thoughts that you would be \nbetter off\n dead OR Hurting yourself in\n some way</string>
    <string name="totals">Add numbers for total</string>
    <string name="section2Header">Section 2</string>
    <string name="section2Header2">Over the last two (2) weeks, how \noften have you been bothered\n by of the following problems? Please input the number that applies to you</string>
    <string name="s2q1">1. Feeling nervous, anxious or\n on edge</string>
    <string name="s2q2">2. Not being able to stop or\n control worrying</string>
    <string name="s2q3">3. Worrying too much about\n different things</string>
    <string name="s2q4">4. Trouble Relaxing</string>
    <string name="s2q5">5. Being so restless that it is hard\n to sit still</string>
    <string name="s2q6">6. Becoming Easily annoyed or irritable</string>
    <string name="s2q7">7. Feeling afraid as if something\n awful might happen</string>
    <string name="section3Header">Section 3</string>
    <string name="section3Header2">In your life have you ever had any experience that was so frightening, horrible or upsetting that in the past month you: (Yes or No)</string>
    <string name="s3q1">1. Have had nightmares about it or\n thought about it when you did not\n want to?</string>
    <string name="StressFormYesOrNo">Enter Yes or No</string>
    <string name="s3q2">2. Tried hard not to think about it or\n went out of your way to avoid situations\n that remind you of it?</string>
    <string name="s3q3">3. Were constantly on guard, watchful\n or easily startled?</string>
    <string name="s3q4">4. Felt numb or detached from others,\n activities, or your surroundings?</string>



</resources>